<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component>
	<content-type>/component/component-software-development</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/Component-software-development.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>4241</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>4241e0c1-0319-b83b-57e1-1669dede2760</objectId>
	<file-name>4241e0c1-0319-b83b-57e1-1669dede2760.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name/>
	<internal-name>SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES en</internal-name>
	<title_s>SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES</title_s>
	<subtitle_s>With a strong team of qualified and experienced programmers implementing software solutions, we always accompany the client for customizing from time to time to bring value to the customer</subtitle_s>
	<software_developer_o item-list="true">	<item>	<title1_s>Accompanying Client</title1_s>
	<describe_s>As soon as we receive a request for a business idea from the business side, our experts and the clients will clarify and analyze all aspects of the requirements to clearly understand and design the best quality services to the client. Likewise, after receiving the information about any issue that arises during the client's operation, we will thoroughly analyze to bring the best solution.</describe_s>
	</item>	<item>	<title1_s>Deploy by period</title1_s>
	<describe_s>Our developers perform step-by-step deployment services to maintain data integrity. DTSVN always aim for readiness and compatibility to meet customer needs from time to time, ensuring the most effective response to business requirements.</describe_s>
	</item>	<item>	<title1_s>Customization and integration capabilities</title1_s>
	<describe_s>Based on the application of modern advanced technology, our solutions are easy to customize with a micro service platform as well as system parameters. That brings benefits for integration and personalization according to customer requirements during the deployment process.</describe_s>
	</item></software_developer_o>
	<createdDate>2025-07-08T04:59:10.340Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2025-07-08T04:59:10.340Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2025-07-08T04:59:10.340Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2025-07-08T04:59:10.340Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
</component>